https://tattoogoo.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content
Free Shipping in U.S. on orders over $49
Your privacy is important, so we have created the following Privacy and Security Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our web site, why we collect it, and how it is used. This Privacy and Security Policy also addresses our data security practices, the options you have to access and control any personally identifiable information you provide to us, and other matters. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by our Terms and Conditions. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy and Security Policy which will be included on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy and Security Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often.
What information do we collect from you? Why?
We may collect information needed to contact you later. If we collect personal contact information (as described below), you may later access and modify it, and remove it from our system. You may also choose simply not to provide your personal contact information at the point of collection.
We may collect your name, address and phone number
When you use our web site, we may request your first and last name, home or other physical address, including your street name and address and name of your city or town, your telephone number or other “real world” contact information.
We use this information to complete, support and analyze your purchases from us and use of the Tattoo Goo web site, for internal purposes and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of the Tattoo Goo web site.
We may collect your email address
We may request your email address, or other information needed to contact you online. We use it to complete, support and analyze your purchases from Tattoo Goo and use of the Tattoo Goo web site, and to comply with any requirements of law. We use it to respond to any questions you might have and to provide you with information about specials occurring on the Tattoo Goo web site if you have chosen this service on the Account Login page. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of the Tattoo Goo website.
We may collect other kinds of information from you
When you use our web site, we may collect personal information about you described below. You may later access and modify the information, or have it removed. You may also simply choose not to provide your personal contact information at the point of collection; however, if you do not provide such information, we will be unable to complete your purchase.
We may collect purchase information
We may collect information actively generated by the purchase of a product or service, such as a payment method. We use this information to process your order and analyze and support your use of the Tattoo Goo web site. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of the Tattoo Goo web site.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf
These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.
What are cookies? Why do we use them?
Cookies are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. Tattoo Goo uses cookies to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to our store. They cannot harm your computer and they do not contain any personal or private information. You must accept cookies to shop at Tattoo Goo.
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. This could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example, making a purchase. Remarketing could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Tattoo Goo website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and, if you like, you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
How do we protect information we collect?
We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our web site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. Tattoo Goo’s servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, and AOL’s browser, so that only Tattoo Goo can read a customer’s personal information.
How long do we keep user information?
We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely.
Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. Note: we have greater control over recently collected data than for archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies.
Your consent to this policy
By using the Tattoo Goo web site, you agree to this Privacy and Security Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy and Security Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting Policy provision. We may change our Privacy and Security Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page which it is your responsibility to review frequently.
Legal disclaimer
This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by Texas law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Texas within one year after the claim arose, or be barred.
If you have a privacy question
If you have a privacy question about the Tattoo Goo web site, please email: info@tattoogoo.com.
Get on the List
Sign up to receive 20% off your first purchase.
First Name*Last Name*Email*
CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
